cloversites.com 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy

## Overview

* * *

**Clover Sites Inc.** , (" **Clover** ", " **Clover Sites** ", " **we** ", " **us** ") is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We have developed this **Privacy Policy** (" **Privacy Policy** ") to ensure your personal information is protected and you understand how any information we do gather or have access to will be treated. The Privacy Policy discloses the information we gather on our website ( **www.cloversites.com** ) (the " **Site** ", " **Sites** "), the ways we process and share such information, and how you can correct or change such information. Except where otherwise expressly indicated herein or on the Site, this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Site and does not apply to information collected as a result of using Clover Sites (the " **Service** ") or outside of the Site. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. We may modify this policy occasionally to keep it up to date with new features and laws, so please check back periodically and become familiar with it.

##### In this document, we'll give you information on these policies and how they affect you:

  1. What Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is collected from me? 
  2. How is my information used? 
  3. With whom will my information be shared? 
  4. How can I access, update or delete my information? 
  5. What else should I know about my privacy? 

### 1\. What Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is collected from me?

Clover Sites makes creating a website simple. Although Users must share some Personally Identifiable Information ("PII"), we have worked to tailor this information and limit access to bona fide Users.

**1.1 Personally Identifiable Information Collected from Individuals.**

We may receive and store any information you enter on the Site or provide to us in any other way through or via the Site that would allow us to identify you personally or contact you. Our use of the PII you provide to us will be in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Examples of PII we may collect from you include:

**1.2 Personally Identifiable Information Collected from Users.**

If you are a " **User** " (as that term is used in the Clover Sites Terms of Service), we will collect name, address, e-mail address, phone number, physical address, and your "Payment Information" information (if applicable, and in accordance with how that term is used in the Clover Sites Terms of Service). We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your organization, experience with the services we provide and contact preferences. Wherever Clover collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. This PII includes:

  * if you sign up as a User, we may ask for and collect your name, e-mail address, and other necessary PII for the service to function.
  * PII you provide about yourself when you send us an e-mail
  * PII you provide about yourself anywhere else on the Site.

**1.3 Passive Gathering of Information Electronically, Cookies, Opting-Out.**

During the course of any visit to the Site, the pages you see are downloaded to your computer. We also utilize various publicly available tools and work with third parties (i.e. Twitter, Facebook, Google) to collect mostly anonymous data, (though in some limited cases, PII or metadata in the form of user-specific or audience-specific data).

  * **1.3.1** \- We use this collective data specifically, as well as in the aggregate, for the purposes of conversion tracking and serving relevant, targeted, information, experiences or advertisements, to certain types or groupings of users, up to and including individual users based on their expressed or inferred interests and publicly-supplied preferences.

  * **1.3.2** \- You can opt out of interest-based advertising or other such third-party tracking mechanisms through any methods that the third-party tools provide as a part of their services. These third-party opt-out techniques may change or be modified by any third party in accordance with their own privacy policy and terms of service, so it is your sole responsibility to verify your privacy and shared information settings with all third party services, and maintain those settings as they are updated.

  * **1.3.3** \- We cannot modify or otherwise control or exclude the information, PII, or other metadata supplied to us by third parties as a result of our use of their services.

  * **1.3.4** \- In addition, "cookies", or other similar anonymous tracking information may be downloaded to your computer during your visit to the site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. These cookies specifically do not contain or collect any PII, and you can set your browser to not accept cookies if you wish. However, if you choose to set your browser to not accept cookies, it may prevent us from providing some features of the Service to you, or at the very least, degrade the overall Site or Service experience.

  * **1.3.5** \- We may automatically collect Site usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of users to the Site, pages visited and similar data. This data is used in the aggregate, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that is intended to identify you personally whenever possible. Aggregate information may be collected through the use of cookies as discussed above. This aggregate information helps Clover Sites assess and improve your experience. This type of aggregate information may be shared with third parties at any time.

**1.4 E-mail Communications.**

When you send an e-mail to Clover Sites, we may retain your e-mail address and the contents of the e-mail you send.

### 2\. How is my information used?

Clover will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. The information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with Clover. When you provide us with your PII, we may use such information for a number of purposes, including:

  * a.) To facilitate communication between Clover and you including, without limitation, responding to your questions or comments, sending e-mails concerning our services, or to contact you for User feedback;
  * b.) To administer your account, process requests, provide services to you, and for Clover product marketing and promotional activities;
  * c.) To provide you with important functionality changes to the Site, new Clover Sites services and special offers from Clover Sites and reputable third parties that we think you will find valuable;
  * d.) To customize, analyze, adjust and improve the Site as may be reasonably required;
  * e.) To enforce our agreements with you, prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities, for other legally permissible purposes and generally to ensure that we comply with applicable laws; and,
  * f.) To send e-mails on your behalf (e.g. to other Users you invite).

If you do not want to receive promotional mailings, simply "opt-out" by the means provided for in the mailings, or by contacting [privacy@cloversites.com](mailto:privacy@cloversites.com).

### 3\. With whom will my information be shared?

Clover may give or share your PII with any third parties under the following circumstances:

**3.1 Fulfillment of Services.**

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include, but are not limited to, companies and individuals who:

  * i.) conduct surveys or promotional activities;
  * ii.) provide customer support, web hosting, internet service, and data analysis; and
  * iii.) others who may assist us from time to time in providing the Service. Such third parties may be provided with access to PII needed to perform their functions but may not use such information for any other purposes.

**3.2 Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection.**

We may disclose any information, including, without limitation, PII that we deem necessary, in our sole discretion and without your prior permission, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.

We may also exchange information, including, without limitation, PII, with other companies and organizations for fraud protection, risk reduction and related activities or to protect the rights, property or safety of Clover Sites, its agents, employees or affiliates or others. Clover Sites reserves the right to disclose PII for a user who we believe is in violation of our Privacy Policy or other terms of service as posted on the Site, even without a subpoena, warrant, court order or other governmental request.

**3.3 Sale or Transfer of Information.**

In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution or sale or transfer of substantially all of the assets of Clover Sites, PII and/or other information collected about you from the Site may be sold, assigned or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the equity and/or assets of Clover Sites in order to permit the party to continue the operation of Clover Sites and/or the Site or any successor version of the Site. By using the Site and providing PII to Clover Sites, you consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph and as reasonably required to complete the transaction.

### 4\. How can I access, update or delete my information?

Clover Sites allows you to view, change, or correct inaccuracies in your PII by logging into your Clover Account (as that term is used in the Clover Sites Terms of Service) and making changes to your PII.

### 5\. What else should I know about my privacy?

**5.1 Third Party Links.**

The Site may contain links to third-party websites. Clover Sites does not control and is not responsible for the information collection practices of such websites, which may differ from those of Clover Sites. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of these web sites before providing any information to them.

**5.2 Data Security.**

We maintain a variety of commercially reasonable safeguards designed to protect your PII from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, we use industry accepted tools and techniques to protect against unauthorized access to our systems. However, Clover Sites does not control the security of other websites on the Internet that you may visit, even when a link appears to those websites from our Site.

In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your PII, we will notify you if reasonably possible and as reasonably necessary so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We will notify you under such circumstances using one or more e-mail addresses if we have one on record for you.

**5.3 Children.**

The Site is not intended for persons under the age of 13. Clover Sites does not knowingly market to, solicit information from, or collect information from any person under the age of 13. If Clover Sites becomes aware that any person submitting information to the Site is under the age of 13, we will attempt to render that person’s (and/or Organization’s) access to the Site inoperable. By using the Site, you hereby represent that you are at least 13 years old.

**5.4 Changes to this Privacy Policy.**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy, we only will notify you by sending an e-mail to one or more of the e-mail address(s) you provided to us and/or by posting notice of the changes on the Site. We recommend that you check the Site periodically for any changes in this Privacy Policy and other policies with changes that may be noticed there.

**5.5 Contacting Us.**

If you have any questions about Clover Sites generally, this Privacy Policy, or the Site, please feel free to contact us by sending an e-mail to [info@cloversites.com](mailto:info@cloversites.com).

**5.6 Users From Outside the United States.**

The Site is hosted in the United States and is governed by United States law. If you are visiting the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to and/or stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located. The data protection and other laws of the United States may differ from those in your country. By using the Site, you consent to the handling of your information by our facilities and those of third party facilities.

**5.7 No Rights of Third Parties.**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.

**LAST UPDATE: JUNE 2, 2015**

_© 2015 Clover Sites, Inc._
